<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Atlanta Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="category_brewerydistillery">Drinks</string>

    <string name="category_marketrestaurant">Food</string>

    <string name="category_parkmuseum">Parks and Rec</string>

    <string name="category_sportstheater">Events</string>


    <!-- Parks, Museums, and Exhibits Section -->

    <string name="name_park_MLK">MLK National Historic Site</string>
    <string name="description_park_MLK">The Martin Luther King Jr. National Historical Park
        consists of several buildings in Atlanta, Georgia, including Martin Luther King Jr.\'s
        boyhood home and the original Ebenezer Baptist Church, the church where King was baptized
        and both his father Martin Luther King Sr. and he were pastors. These places, critical to
        the interpretation of the life of Martin Luther King Jr. and his legacy as a leader of
        the American Civil Rights Movement, were included in the park when it was established
        on October 10, 1980.</string>
    <string name="address_park_MLK">450 Auburn Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30312</string>

    <string name="name_park_Zoo">Zoo Atlanta</string>
    <string name="description_park_zoo">Zoo Atlanta is an Association of Zoos and Aquariums
        accredited zoological park in Atlanta, Georgia. It was founded in 1889 when a local
        businessman purchased a bankrupt traveling circus and donated the animals to the city
        of Atlanta. The zoo is currently one of four zoos in the USA housing giant pandas.</string>
    <string name="address_park_zoo">800 Cherokee Avenue SE, Atlanta, GA 30315</string>

    <string name="name_park_aquarium">Georgia Aquarium</string>
    <string name="description_park_aquarium">The Georgia Aquarium is a public aquarium in Atlanta,
        Georgia, USA. It houses more than a hundred thousand animals and represents several
        thousand species, all of which reside in 10 million US gallons (38,000 m3) of marine and
        salt water. It was the largest aquarium in the world from its opening in 2005
        until 2012, when it was surpassed by Marine Life Park in Singapore. The Aquarium's notable
        specimens include whale sharks, beluga whales, California sea lions, bottlenose dolphins,
        and manta rays.</string>
    <string name="address_park_aquarium">225 Baker St NW, Atlanta, GA 30313</string>
    
    <string name="name_park_coke">World of Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="description_park_coke">The World of Coca-Cola is a museum, located in Atlanta,
        Georgia, showcasing the history of The Coca-Cola Company. The 20-acre complex
        opened to the public on May 24, 2007, relocating to 121 Baker Street in Atlanta, just
        blocks away from where John Pemberton created the original Coca-Cola formula. The museum
        houses thousands of Coca-Cola artifacts and many exhibits including one about the 
        secret formula of Coca-Cola.</string>
    <string name="address_park_coke">121 Baker St NW, Atlanta, GA 30313</string>
    
    <string name="name_park_piedmont">Piedmont Park</string>
    <string name="description_park_piedmont">Piedmont Park is an urban park in Atlanta, Georgia,
        located about 1 mile (1.6 km) northeast of Downtown, between the Midtown and Virginia
        Highland neighborhoods. Over the years, the park has also served as an athletic center 
        for the city. Atlanta\'s first professional baseball team, the Atlanta Crackers, played 
        in the park from 1902 to 1904. Several important intercollegiate rivalries were also 
        forged in the park including the University of Georgia vs. Georgia Tech baseball rivalry 
        and Georgia versus Auburn football which has been called the "Deep South\'s Oldest Rivalry".</string>
    <string name="address_park_piedmont">400 Park Dr NE, Atlanta, GA 30306</string>
    
    <string name="name_park_beltline">The Beltline</string>
    <string name="description_park_beltline">The BeltLine is a former railway corridor around the
        core of Atlanta, Georgia, under development in stages as a multi-use trail. Some portions
        are already complete, while others are still in a rough state but hikeable. Using existing
        rail track easements, the BeltLine is designed to improve transportation, add green space,
        and promote redevelopment. There are longer-term visions for streetcar or light-rail lines
        along all or part of the corridor. The BeltLine plan was originally developed in 1999 as
        a masters thesis by Georgia Tech student Ryan Gravel. It links city parks and
        neighborhoods, but has also been used for temporary art installations. In 2013, the
        project received a federal grant of $18 million to develop the southwest corridor.</string>
    <string name="address_park_beltline">Atlanta, GA (multiple locations)</string>

    <string name="name_park_botanical">Atlanta Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="description_park_botanical">The Atlanta Botanical Garden is a 30 acre botanical
        garden incorporated in 1976 and located adjacent to Piedmont Park in Midtown Atlanta,
        Georgia, United States. The garden hosts seasonal events and exhibits year round, and is 
        famous for its Chihuly in the Garden and Lights in the Garden exhibits.</string>
    <string name="address_park_botanical">1345 Piedmont Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>
    
    <string name="name_park_woodruff">Woodruff Arts Center</string>
    <string name="description_park_woodruff">Woodruff Arts Center is a visual and performing arts
        center located in Atlanta, Georgia. The center houses three not-for-profit arts divisions
        on one campus. Opened in 1968, the Woodruff Arts Center is home to the Alliance Theatre,
        the Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, and the High Museum of Art.</string>
    <string name="address_park_woodruff">1280 Peachtree Street Northeast, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>

    <string name="name_park_fernbank">Fernbank Museum of Natural History</string>
    <string name="description_park_fernbank">Fernbank Museum of Natural History, in Atlanta, is a
        museum that presents exhibitions and programming about natural history that are meant to
        entertain as well as educate the public. Its mission is to encourage a greater appreciation
        of the planet and its people. Fernbank Museum has a number of permanent exhibitions and
        regularly hosts temporary exhibitions in its expansive facility, designed by Graham Gund
        Architects. Giants of the Mesozoic, on display in the atrium of Fernbank Museum, features
        a 123-foot (37 m) long Argentinosaurus, the largest dinosaur ever classified; as well as
        a Giganotosaurus. The permanent exhibition, A Walk Through Time in Georgia, tells the
        twofold story of Georgia's natural history and the development of the planet.</string>
    <string name="address_park_fernbank">767 Clifton Rd, Atlanta, GA 30307</string>


    <!-- Sports and Theaters Section -->

    <string name="name_theater_mercedes">Mercedes-Benz Stadium</string>
    <string name="description_theater_mercedes">The Mercedes-Benz Stadium is a multi-purpose
        retractable roof stadium located in Atlanta, Georgia. The home of the Atlanta Falcons
        of the National Football League (NFL) and the Atlanta United FC of Major League Soccer
        (MLS), it replaced the adjacent NFL indoor arena Georgia Dome (now demolished), the
        Falcons\' home stadium from 1992 through 2016. Mercedes-Benz stadium holds the record
        of the world\'s largest halo board and is one of few football stadiums with
        retractable roofs. The stadium is owned by the state of Georgia through the Georgia
        World Congress Center Authority, and operated by AMB Group, the parent organization of
        the Falcons and Atlanta United. The total cost was estimated at $1.6 billion, as of
        June 2016. The stadium officially opened on August 26, 2017 with a Falcons preseason
        game against the Arizona Cardinals, despite the retractable roof system being
        incomplete at the time.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_mercedes">1 AMB Dr NW, Atlanta, GA 30313</string>

    <string name="name_theater_philips">Philips Arena</string>
    <string name="description_theater_philips">Philips Arena is a multi-purpose indoor arena
        located in Atlanta, Georgia, and is home to the Atlanta Hawks, of the National Basketball
        Association, and the Atlanta Dream, of the Women\'s National Basketball Association.
        It also served as home to the National Hockey League\'s Atlanta Thrashers from 1999 to
        2011, before the team moved to Winnipeg. It opened in 1999 at a cost of $213.5 million,
        replacing the Omni Coliseum. It is owned by the Atlanta Fulton County Recreation Authority
        and operated by Tony Ressler, who also, with a group of investors that includes Grant
        Hill, owns the Hawks.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_philips">1 Philips Dr, Atlanta, GA 30303</string>

    <string name="name_theater_tabernacle">The Tabernacle</string>
    <string name="description_theater_tabernacle">Tabernacle, is a mid-size concert hall
        in the U.S. city of Atlanta. The Tabernacle has been a venue for notable acts, including
        Guns N\' Roses, The Black Crowes, Adele, Eminem, Kendrick Lamar, Robbie Williams, Alice
        in Chains, Bob Dylan, Prince and The New Power Generation, The 1975 and Atlanta\'s own
        Mastodon, and Blackberry Smoke. Along with music concerts, the venue also holds many
        comedy tours annually including Bob Saget, Lisa Lampanelli, Cheech and Chong and Stephen
        Lynch. The Tabernacle is managed by concert promoter Live Nation and has a seating
        capacity of 2,600 people.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_tabernacle">152 Luckie St NW, Atlanta, GA 30303</string>

    <string name="name_theater_center">Center Stage Theater</string>
    <string name="description_theater_center">Center Stage is a mid-sized concert complex
        comprising three separate venues located in Atlanta, Georgia. Originally known as
        Theatre Atlanta, the concert hall was built in memorial to a young theater enthusiast.
        Upon its opening in the fall of 1966, the building functioned as a performing arts
        theater, but has since become primarily music-focused. In the 2000s, Center Stage
        evolved dramatically and two new venues were added to the building. All three venues
        feature a wide variety of musical acts, as well as comedy shows and theatrical
        performances.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_center">1374 West Peachtree Street Northwest, Atlanta, GA
        30309</string>

    <string name="name_theater_variety">Variety Playhouse</string>
    <string name="description_theater_variety">The Variety Playhouse (originally known as the 
        Euclid Theatre) is a music venue in Atlanta, Georgia, United States. It is located on 
        Euclid Avenue and features a variety of music acts including rock, indie, electronic, 
        funk, country, folk, bluegrass, jazz, blues and world music as well as other live 
        shows.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_variety">1099 Euclid Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30307</string>
    
    <string name="name_theater_fox">The Fox Theater</string>
    <string name="description_theater_fox">The Fox Theatre (often marketed as the Fabulous Fox),
        a former movie palace, is a performing arts venue located at 660 Peachtree Street NE in
        Midtown Atlanta, Georgia, and is the centerpiece of the Fox Theatre Historic District.
        The theater was originally planned as part of a large Shrine Temple as evidenced by its
        Moorish design. The 4,665 seat auditorium was ultimately developed as a lavish movie
        theater in the Fox Theatres chain and opened in 1929. It hosts a variety of cultural
        and artistic events including the Atlanta Ballet, a summer film series, and performances
        by national touring companies of Broadway shows. The venue also hosts occasional concerts
        by popular artists.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_fox">660 W Peachtree St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308</string>

    <string name="name_theater_eddie">Eddie\'s Attic</string>
    <string name="description_theater_eddie">Eddie\'s Attic is a music club in Decatur, Georgia.
        Founded in 1992 by Eddie Owen, it is a venue for both local musical talent and musicians
        of some acclaim who often got their start in the Atlanta area. Artists who developed
        their fanbase at Eddie\'s Attic include Shawn Mullins, Sugarland, Michelle Malone,
        Justin Bieber, disappear fear, The Civil Wars, John Mayer and Crystal Bowersox. Eddie\'s
        Attic also hosts a bi-annual songwriting contest, the Eddie's Attic Open Mic Shootout,
        where musical acts from around the United States compete to win a $1000 prize. Former
        winners of the contest include John Mayer, Shawn Mullins, Clay Cook, Jennifer Nettles
        of Sugarland, Jennifer Daniels, The Brilliant Inventions and Whitney Monge.</string>
    <string name="address_theater_eddie">515 N McDonough St, Decatur, GA 30030</string>



    <!-- Restaurants and Markets Section-->

    <string name="name_restaurant_ponce">Ponce City Market</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_ponce">Ponce City Market is a mixed-use development
        located in a historic building in Atlanta, with national and local retail anchors,
        restaurants, a food hall, boutiques and offices, and residential units. It is located
        where the BeltLine crosses Ponce de Leon Avenue in the Old Fourth Ward where that
        neighborhood touches the Virginia Highland, Poncey-Highland and Midtown neighborhoods.
        The 2,100,000-square-foot (200,000 m2) building, one of the largest by volume in the
        Southeast United States, was used by Sears, Roebuck and Co. from 1926–1987 and later
        by the City of Atlanta as "City Hall East". The building's lot covers 16 acres
        (65,000 m2). It officially opened on August 25, 2014. It was listed on the
        National Register of Historic Places in 2016.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_ponce">675 Ponce De Leon Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30308</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_krog">Krog Street Market</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_krog">Krog Street Market is a 9-acre mixed-use development
        in Atlanta, located along the BeltLine trail at Edgewood Avenue in Inman Park which opened
        in Summer 2014. The complex is centered on a 12,000-square-foot, west coast-style market
        and restaurants, and also includes up to 300 apartments. The marketplace has been planned
        to have four or five restaurants and merchants such as florists, cheesemakers, butchers,
        and bakers under one roof.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_krog">99 Krog St NE, Atlanta, GA 30307</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_vortex">The Vortex Bar and Grill</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_vortex">The Vortex Bar and Grill is a restaurant in
        Atlanta, Georgia, with two locations, in Midtown on Peachtree Street, originally opened
        in 1992, and Little Five Points, opened in 1996 and distinguished by the large "Laughing
        Skull" entrance. The restaurant is famous for its burgers and has been featured on
        Season 1 of the Travel Channel\'s Man vs. Food.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_vortex">438 Moreland Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30307</string>
    
    <string name="name_restaurant_parkers">Parker\'s on Ponce</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_parkers">An upscale steakhouse decorated with cool colors 
        and dark woods, with sides like lobster mac and cheese, and a high-end selection of beers
        and spirits.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_parkers">116 E Ponce de Leon Ave, Decatur, GA 30030</string>
    
    <string name="name_restaurant_brick">Brick Store Pub</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_brick">A neighborhood pub serving fish and chips and
        burgers with an extensive beer menu and an upstairs Belgian Bar.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_brick">125 E Court Square, Decatur, GA 30030</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_caravaca">Caravaca Market</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_caravaca">Harry\'s Caravaca Market is the newest, most
        creative gourmet food hall in Atlanta. Our 6000 square-foot space includes various food
        stations, a provisions market area and an outdoor patio. The food hall features seasonal
        cultural events focused on US regions and other countries. Caravaca Market not only offers
        locally sourced international flavors, but a place for Atlanta residents and visitors to
        gather and socialize. </string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_caravaca">782 Peachtree Street NE, Atlanta, GA 30308</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_cypress">Cypress Street Pint and Plate</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_cypress">A rotating lineup of beers on tap pairs with
        hearty American grub at a relaxed tavern with a patio.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_cypress">817 W Peachtree St NW, Atlanta, GA 30308</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_jct">JCT Kitchen</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_jct">Updated Southern fare in hip space with late-night 
        live music, plus upstairs bar with skyline view.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_jct">1198 Howell Mill Rd #18, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>
    
    <string name="name_restaurant_star">Star Provisions Market and Cafe</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_star">Star Provisions Market and Cafe is the culinary
        dream shop for the gourmet expert and novice alike. Featuring individual markets for
        baked goods, cheese, meats, seafood, locally roasted coffee, and other gourmet food items,
        an array of gifts and cookware, and a bustling breakfast, lunch and dinner counter, Star
        Provisions sources and stocks the highest quality products, including fresh cut meats,
        fish, cheese, freshly baked breads, and sweets.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_star">1460 Ellsworth Industrial Blvd, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>
    
    <string name="name_restaurant_hf">Holeman and Finch Public House</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_hf">Modern gastropub with new takes on vintage eats such
        as deviled eggs, plus custom cocktails.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_hf">2277 Peachtree Rd NW, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_verde">Verde Taqueria</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_verde">Mexican eatery draws groups with a varied menu,
        margaritas and a contemporary space with a patio.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_verde">1426 Dresden Dr NE, Atlanta, GA 30319</string>
    
    <string name="name_restaurant_south">South City Kitchen</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_south">Set in a 1920s bungalow, this eatery offers
        inventive takes on Southern favorites plus a fireplace.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_south">1144 Crescent Ave NE, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_einstein">Einstein\'s</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_einstein">Eatery offering creative takes on Southern
        comfort classics, with a patio and popular weekend brunch.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_einstein">1077 Juniper St NE, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>

    <string name="name_restaurant_zocalo">Zocalo Cantina</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_zocalo">Chef Richard Sandoval offers upscale Mexican
        comfort food and many tequilas in casual, stylish space.</string>
    <string name="address_restaurant_zocalo">187 10th St NE, Atlanta, GA 30309</string>



    <!-- Breweries and Distilleries Section-->

    <string name="name_brewery_sweetwater">Sweetwater Brewing Co.</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_sweetwater">Boisterous, indoor-outdoor microbrewery with
        tours and taproom plus live music and a dog-friendly patio.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_sweetwater">195 Ottley Dr NE, Atlanta, GA 30324</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_monday">Monday Night Brewing</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_monday">Casual craft brewery featuring a spacious,
        high-ceiling tasting room and regular tours.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_monday">670 Trabert Ave NW, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>
    
    <string name="name_brewery_red">Red Brick Brewing Co</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_red">West Atlanta microbrewery with an outdoor patio
        and a rotating selection of craft beers.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_red">2323 Defoor Hills Rd NW, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_scofflaw">Scofflaw Brewing Co.</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_scofflaw">Scofflaw is a band of brewing compatriots
        dedicated to innovation, craftsmanship and expanding the horizons of craft beer
        in the Southeast.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_scofflaw">1738 MacArthur Blvd NW, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_second">Second Self Beer Company</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_second">Second Self Beer Company, Georgia\'s fast growing
        craft brewery located in Atlanta, GA making exciting beers designed with food in mind</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_second">1317 Logan Cir NW, Atlanta, GA 30318</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_taverns">Three Taverns Craft Brewery</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_taverns">Three Taverns is a Georgia brewery delivering
        an open-minded American interpretation of traditional Belgian-style beers
        and more.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_taverns">121 New St, Decatur, GA 30030</string>
    
    <string name="name_brewery_wild">Wild Heaven Beer</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_wild">Wild Heaven focuses on an all-grain, no adjunct-sugar
        brewing philosophy to create bigger flavor without excess alcohol.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_wild">135 Maple St B, Avondale Estates, GA 30002</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_eventide">Eventide Brewing</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_eventide">Cozy microbrewery located in historic Grant Park
        serving creative craft beers.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_eventide">1015 Grant St SE, Atlanta, GA 30315</string>
    
    <string name="name_brewery_oldfourth">Old Fourth Distillery</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_oldfourth">Old Fourth Distillery is a Craft Distillery
        featuring Vodka and Gin. located in the Old Fourth Ward Area of Atlanta.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_oldfourth">487 Edgewood Ave SE, Atlanta, GA 30312</string>

    <string name="name_brewery_asw">Atlanta Spirit Works</string>
    <string name="description_brewery_asw">Creating world-class southern inspired versions of
        spirits from all over the world.</string>
    <string name="address_brewery_asw">199 Armour Dr NE, Atlanta, GA 30324</string>
</resources>
